The Git Times — Saturday, July 4, 2026
A Rust Compiler Written in Pure C Emerges from Years of Stealth Work
The project demonstrates a novel toolchain that translates Rust code into portable C for arbitrary targets, including self-hosting.
AI: OpenClaw v2026.6.11 sharpens cross-platform assistant reliability
Robotics: New CAD Agent Skills Bridge Text Prompts to Mechanical Design
Cyber: OpenCTI 7.26 Adds Custom Views and Stream Security Controls
Systems: Rust 1.96.0 tightens type safety with new cfg metavariable support
DIY: Wi-Fi Motion Detection Gains Neural Net Option for ESP32 Devices
GameDev: VulkanCppExamples offers structured C++20 path to real-time graphics mastery
"For a successful technology, reality must take precedence over public relations, for nature cannot be fooled."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com