The Git Times — Friday, July 24, 2026
Repowise Cuts Agent Context Load by 96% with Precomputed Code Intelligence
Local, self-hosted tool indexes codebases once to eliminate redundant AI exploration and reduce token usage
AI: Netdata v2.10.4 bolsters macOS monitoring with hardware sensor collectors
Robotics: Autoware Universe expands autonomous driving toolkit with ROS2 planner upgrades
Cyber: OpenCTI Platform Redesigns Connector Catalog as Faceted Marketplace in Latest Release
Systems: Bun v1.3.14 sharpens TypeScript and JSX handling for faster dev cycles
DIY: HackRF Pro Gains Larger SPI Flash Access in Latest Firmware Update
GameDev: Noble Shader Pack Adds Pathtracing to Minecraft with Performance Focus
"The major problems of the world are the result of the difference between how nature works and the way people think."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com