The Git Times — Thursday, July 16, 2026
Tauri 2.11.5 Sharpens Desktop App Performance with Rust Backend
Framework blends web frontends with native binaries for secure, lightweight cross-platform apps
AI: n8n Tightens MCP Workflow Execution Controls in Latest Patch
Robotics: YARP 3.12.3 Closes 3.x Series with Simulation and IPC Enhancements
Cyber: HackTricks Wiki Gains Japanese Search Index Boost
Systems: Bun's Rust-Powered Toolkit Gains Traction as Node.js Alternative
DIY: ESPectre's Ping for Reliable Wi-Fi Motion Detection Without Cameras
GameDev: NonToon Blends PBR and NPR for Flexible Character Shaders
"New technology is not additive; it is ecological. A new medium does not add something; it changes everything."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com