The Git Times — Friday, July 17, 2026
OmniRoute Solves AI Tool Fragmentation with Unified Free Gateway
One endpoint connects Claude Code, Copilot, and 231+ providers with token compression and auto-fallback
AI: n8n tightens security with SES signing and package provenance checks
Robotics: Rerun 0.34.1 Tightens Real-Time Robotics Data Sync Across Modalities
Cyber: OpenCTI Adds Live Stream Fixes as Cyber Threat Intelligence Tooling Matures
Systems: Bun 1.3.14 sharpens TypeScript and JSX performance in single binary
DIY: TuyaOpen v1.8.0 Adds AI Image Generation and Local Printer Support
GameDev: PlayCanvas Engine Refines Gaussian Splatting Support in Latest Patch
"Consider what the world would lose if each mind were to do its own indexing."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com