The Git Times — Monday, July 20, 2026
QwenPaw’s MCP Integration Unlocks Seamless Tool Orchestration for Local AI Agents
The latest release enables secure, credential-aware connections to external services without compromising local data sovereignty.
AI: n8n 2.30.8 patches AI agent tool visibility in human-in-the-loop workflows
Robotics: Image-search bot adapts to modern QQ bot standards after eight years
Cyber: OpenCTI Platform Refines Live Stream Filtering in Latest Release
Systems: ClickHouse 26.3 LTS Release Strengthens Real-Time Analytics for Cloud Workloads
DIY: Raspberry Pi Flight Tracker v2 Adds Pi 5 Support After Major Rewrite
GameDev: GDevelop’s CLI Integration Streamlines Game Dev Workflows
"Tools for conviviality are those which give each person who uses them the greatest opportunity to enrich the environment with the fruits of their vision."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com