The Git Times — Tuesday, July 7, 2026
FFmpeg’s Silent Engine Powers Modern Streaming Infrastructure
The decades-old multimedia framework underpins real-time video pipelines across cloud, edge, and broadcast systems
AI: n8n’s AI-native workflow platform gains enterprise traction with flexible model switching
Robotics: commaai/openpilot Adds Rivian 2025 Support, Expands ADAS Reach
Cyber: Wazuh Tightens Cluster Security in Latest Release
Systems: TensorFlow 2.21 Drops Python 3.9 Support, Adds JPEG XL and Quantized Ops
DIY: HackRF Pro Gains SPI Flash Access in Latest Firmware Patch
GameDev: PlayCanvas Engine Patches GPU Instability in Latest 3D Gaussian Splatting Release
"The real problem is not whether machines think but whether men do."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com