The Git Times — Sunday, July 12, 2026
GitHub Project Decodes Windows' Hidden Global Device Identifier
Reverse-engineers Microsoft's persistent GDID telemetry, revealing how it's generated, stored, and transmitted in Windows 11
AI: OpenClaw v2026.6.11 Tames Messaging Chaos for Personal AI Assistants
Robotics: commaai/openpilot adds Rivian, Acura support in v0.11.1
Cyber: OpenCTI Refines Cyber Threat Intelligence Workflow with Custom Views and Accessibility Upgrades
Systems: Netdata v2.10.3 fixes critical eBPF memory leak under process churn
DIY: LiteX 2026.04 Fixes SD Card and CPU Core Stability in FPGA Builds
GameDev: Material Maker’s GraphEdit workflow gains SVG icons and tab flexibility
"We drive into the future using only our rearview mirror."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com