The Git Times — Thursday, July 23, 2026
Syncthing Adds Proxy Support and Session Controls in v2.1
New grouping and block indexing options improve usability and efficiency for peer-to-peer file sync
AI: OpenClaw v2026.7.1 Rewrites Onboarding and Control UI for Local AI Assistants
Robotics: Gazebo Sim Jetty Release Boosts ROS2 Integration for Real-World Robot Testing
Cyber: OpenCTI revamps connector catalog into marketplace for threat intel workflows
Systems: UV 0.11.31 Adds Workspace Cross-Referencing and Malware Checks for Python Devs
DIY: HackRF Pro Gains Larger SPI Flash Access in Firmware Update
GameDev: PlayCanvas Engine Adds Gaussian Splatting Support and XR Improvements in v2.21.0
"The purpose of a system is what it does."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com