The Git Times — Sunday, June 28, 2026
Chinese Fiction Pipeline Automates Novel Writing with LLMs
A Python workflow distills genre fiction templates into reusable prompts for AI-assisted storytelling
AI: Model Context Protocol gains traction through curated server implementations
Robotics: iDynTree Powers Floating-Base Robot Dynamics with Flexible Base-Link Handling
Cyber: ProxyBridge v4.0.0 Brings IPv6 and Profile Management to Windows Proxy Routing
Systems: PowerToys Fixes Command Palette Memory Leak in v0.100.2
DIY: DIY Synth List Powers Open-Source Hardware Music Makers
GameDev: Real-Time Water Simulation Bridges Three.js and Advanced Optics
"The question concerning technology is never merely technical."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com