The Git Times — Wednesday, July 15, 2026
Codex Skill Automates Full Paper-Cut Ad Production from Script to MP4
Integrates voice cloning, animation, and quality checks into a single OpenAI Codex workflow for localized ad creation
AI: PyTorch 2.13.0 Boosts Distributed Training with Fault-Tolerant Comms
Robotics: Drake Integrates SNOPT Solver to Boost Robotic Motion Planning Precision
Cyber: Yakit’s Yaklang Scripting Unifies Red and Blue Team Workflows
Systems: ClickHouse 25.8 LTS Release Boosts Real-Time Analytics for AI Workloads
DIY: Insect Detect v2.0.0 Brings Real-Time AI to DIY Wildlife Monitoring
GameDev: NonToon Bridges PBR and NPR for Hybrid Game Visuals
"The information you have is not the information you want. The information you want is not the information you need."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com