The Git Times — Thursday, July 9, 2026
MIRA Simulates Rocket League Matches Inside a 5B Parameter World Model
Real-time 2v2 gameplay generated from player actions via latent diffusion on a single GPU
AI: OpenClaw v2026.6.11 fixes channel reliability for personal AI assistants
Robotics: Google DeepMind Releases MuJoCo 3.10.0 with MJX GPU Acceleration
Cyber: OWASP Juice Shop Adds Node.js v26 Support for Modern Dev Workflows
Systems: Zed Editor Integrates Local AI via llama.cpp for Offline Coding Assistance
DIY: Raspberry Pi Flight Tracker gains hardware-specific installers for Pi 5 support
GameDev: Super Mario Bros Remastered Adds Level Metadata and Controller Tweaks
"The art challenges the technology, and the technology inspires the art."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com