The Git Times — Monday, June 29, 2026
Prometheus v3.12.0 Hardens Security and Expands Cloud Discovery
Latest release fixes critical vulnerabilities, enhances PromQL with start-timestamp functions, and adds service discovery for major cloud providers.
AI: Microsoft's open data science curriculum remains a foundational resource for self-taught analysts
Robotics: ROS Image Pipeline Bridges Camera Data to Vision Workflows After a Decade
Cyber: Sniffnet Brings Rust-Powered Network Visibility to Every Developer Desktop
Systems: Self-Hosted Notes Gain Momentum with Mobile-First Improvements
DIY: Hardware Locality Project Enables Precise CPU and Memory Mapping in HPC
GameDev: Real-Time Water Simulation Brings Cinematic Fluidity to Three.js
"Everywhere we remain unfree and chained to technology, whether we passionately affirm or deny it."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com