The Git Times — Monday, July 6, 2026
GameBlocks Gives AI Agents Concrete 3D Building Blocks for Browser Games
Provides inspectable modules for spatial logic, letting coding agents prototype game mechanics without deriving 3D behavior from scratch
AI: OpenClaw v2026.6.11 Fixes Cross-Platform Messaging Glitches
Robotics: Isaac Lab 3.0 Beta 2 Patch 1 Aligns with Isaac Sim 6.0.1
Cyber: Wazuh tightens cluster security after recent vulnerability fixes
Systems: Bun v1.3.14 sharpens JavaScript toolchain with faster install and test commands
DIY: Automotive Skills Suite Standardizes Engineering Artifacts with Paired Reviewers
GameDev: PlayCanvas Engine Adds Gaussian Splatting Support for Real-Time 3D Rendering
"It has become appallingly obvious that our technology has exceeded our humanity."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com