The Git Times — Friday, June 26, 2026
OpenFugu Unlocks Sakana's Closed LLM Orchestrator for Public Use
Reverse-engineers Fugu's model-routing policy into a trainable, serveable open system
AI: AI Engineering Curriculum Builds Skills From Math to Agents
Robotics: AI Agents Gain Practical CAD Skills for Real-World Fabrication
Cyber: BBOT’s recursive depth gives security teams an edge in subdomain discovery
Systems: whisper.cpp Powers Offline Speech Recognition Across Embedded Devices
DIY: Optocam Zero blends retro charm with modern Pi Zero utility
GameDev: Jolt Physics Enables Thread-Safe Collision Queries During Simulation
"New technology is not additive; it is ecological. A new medium does not add something; it changes everything."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com