The Git Times — Tuesday, June 30, 2026
Scrcpy v4.0 Shifts to SDL3, Refines Android Screen Mirroring
Latest release adds flex display, camera torch, and HID improvements while dropping SDL2 legacy
AI: PyTorch 2.12.1 patches GPU memory bugs on NVIDIA B200/B100 chips
Robotics: Openpilot expands vehicle support with Acura and Rivian models
Cyber: Infisical’s Secret Syncs Streamline Multi-Platform Configuration Management
Systems: Kubernetes v1.36.2 Refines Scheduling with GPU-Aware Workload Controls
DIY: MiniBolt Adds Tor Onion Access to Bitcoin Node Guide
GameDev: GodSVG refines SVG editing with real-time, metadata-free code sync
"Tools for conviviality are those which give each person who uses them the greatest opportunity to enrich the environment with the fruits of their vision."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com