The Git Times — Thursday, June 25, 2026
Bohemia Interactive Open-Sources Classic Arma Engine Codebase
Modernized C++20 release enables community study, modification, and extension of 2001 military simulator foundation
AI: Gemini CLI Integrates MCP for Custom AI Agent Extensions
Robotics: URDF Studio streamlines robot modeling with visual editing and AI assistance
Cyber: OpenZeppelin Contracts remains the bedrock of secure EVM development
Systems: RAGFlow Fuses Agent Logic with Retrieval for Production LLM Context
DIY: Automotive Skills Suite Turns AI Into Structured Engineering Deliverables
GameDev: EnTT's latest update sharpens C++ ECS with zero-cost type safety
"The information you have is not the information you want. The information you want is not the information you need."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com