The Git Times — Thursday, July 9, 2026
ZML Bridges AI Models to Any Hardware via Zig and MLIR
Compiles models directly to NVIDIA, AMD, Intel, TPU, and Trainium with zero code changes
AI: OpenClaw v2026.6.11 sharpens personal AI assistant reliability
Robotics: Dora-rs v0.5.0 sharpens Rust robotics with Zenoh SHM and Arrow
Cyber: OpenCTI Enhances Telemetry and Connector Visibility in Latest Release
Systems: ClickHouse Cloud gains traction as enterprises shift analytics workloads
DIY: PiKVM's Raspberry Pi-based IP-KVM gains traction as remote server access matures
GameDev: Babylon.js 9.16 sharpens WebGPU support and audio precision
"The art challenges the technology, and the technology inspires the art."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com