The Git Times — Tuesday, July 21, 2026
AppLess Reimagines Mobile UIs as Instant, LLM-Generated Experiences
A generative UI prototype that builds native screens on demand using OpenUI and LLMs, no apps required
AI: n8n 2.31.4 fixes workflow group handling in AI automation platform
Robotics: Dora-rs v0.5.0 sharpens Rust robotics middleware with Zenoh SHM gains
Cyber: Cilium 1.19.6 refines eBPF networking with Gateway API and IPv6 fixes
Systems: TensorFlow 2.21 Drops Python 3.9 Support and TensorBoard Dependency
DIY: BruceDevices Firmware Adds NetCut-Inspired ARP Module for WiFi Attacks
GameDev: Egui’s inspection protocol opens GUI apps to AI agent control
"Technology is not a neutral tool. It is a system that carries its own values."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com