The Git Times — Saturday, June 27, 2026
New Texture Ripper Lets Developers Extract Game Assets from Screenshots
DinoRip simplifies texture atlas creation for retro game modders and asset builders
AI: Dify’s CLI Tool Lets Developers Run AI Workflows From Terminal
Robotics: TorchRL’s modular design lets RL builders scale from prototype to production
Cyber: Azure Sentinel's Open Repository Powers Enterprise Threat Hunting at Scale
Systems: Claw Code Shows How AI Agents Can Maintain Rust Projects Autonomously
DIY: DeskHop Enables Seamless Mouse-Driven Desktop Switching Across OSes
GameDev: Real-time water simulation brings cinematic effects to Three.js
"Consider what the world would lose if each mind were to do its own indexing."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com