The Git Times — Thursday, July 2, 2026
AI Coding Agents Now Learn From Their Own Hard-Won Debugging Sessions
Self-learning-skills captures reusable operational knowledge from \*
AI: Gradio Simplifies ML App Deployment for Python Developers
Robotics: TLSFuzzer gains Python 3.6+ support while dropping legacy Python 2.6 compatibility
Cyber: OpenCTI 7.26 Adds Custom Views and Stream Deny Lists for CTI Teams
Systems: TensorFlow 2.21 Drops Python 3.9, Adds JPEG XL and Int2 Support
DIY: RealSense SDK adds Jetson-optimized close-range depth and ROS2 compression
GameDev: Dear ImGui v1.92.8 sharpens immediate-mode GUI toolkit for embedded workflows
"We are as gods and might as well get good at it."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com