The Git Times — Wednesday, June 24, 2026
Deno 2.8.3 sharpens TypeScript-first runtime with security and tooling upgrades
Latest release refines crypto, telemetry, and node compatibility while reinforcing Deno’s secure-by-default ethos for modern JS/TS development
AI: n8n Balances Code Flexibility with AI Workflow Automation
Robotics: Comma AI's Openpilot Expands Driver Assist to New EV Models
Cyber: Trickest/cve Automates CVE PoC Collection for Rapid Exploit Discovery
Systems: llama.cpp adds native MXFP4 support for gpt-oss models
DIY: GDSFactory streamlines hardware design from code to fabrication
GameDev: MustardOS/internal Provides Core Infrastructure for Embedded Linux Systems
"Technology is the knack of so arranging the world that we don't have to experience it."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com