The Git Times — Wednesday, July 1, 2026
Zed’s AI-Powered Multiplayer Editing Reaches New Maturity
Rust-based editor adds worktree creation and terminal automation to collaborative coding workflows
AI: Scikit-learn 1.9.0 Adds Narwhals for Broader DataFrame Support
Robotics: Drake’s SNOPT Integration Boosts Precision in Robotic Motion Planning
Cyber: Maigret Expands OSINT Reach with Proxy Integration and Recursive Search
Systems: TensorFlow 2.21 Drops Python 3.9, Adds JPEG XL and int2 Support
DIY: Photobooth App Adds Rclone Sync for Seamless Media Backup
GameDev: SpacetimeDB v2.6.0 adds primary key support for views across key languages
"Civilization advances by extending the number of important operations which we can perform without thinking about them."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com