The Git Times — Saturday, July 11, 2026
OpenConnector Unifies SaaS Access for AI Agents Without Exposing Credentials
Open-source gateway delivers 1,000+ prebuilt Actions via SDK, CLI, MCP, and HTTP while keeping auth local and inspectable
AI: OpenClaw v2026.6.11 Fixes Messaging Glitches Across Major Platforms
Robotics: Drake's Latest Release Integrates SNOPT Solver for Precise Robot Motion Planning
Cyber: Community Scripts Simplifies Proxmox VE Deployments with One-Command Installs
Systems: Rust 1.97.0 refines language semantics and stabilizes niche hardware features
DIY: Raspberry Pi Flight Tracker v2 Adds Pi 5 Support After Major Rewrite
GameDev: Flecs v4.1.6 Adds Data-Oriented Hierarchies and Entity Range API
"The medium is the message."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com